import '../classes/quiz_class.dart';

List<QuizQuestion> dragonBallQuestions = [
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Beerus ate wasabi and reacted to it, who one-hit Beerus to sleep?",
      answer1: "Vegeta",
      answer2: "Goku",
      answer3: "Whis",
      answer4: "Grad Priest",
      correctAnswer: "Whis"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Goku Black created this Energy Blade with his anger. What is this Scythe called?",
      answer1: "Demon Scythe",
      answer2: "Sickle of Sorrow",
      answer3: "Sickle of Sins",
      answer4: "Scythe of Destruction",
      correctAnswer: "Sickle of Sorrow"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Cell regurgitated (threw up) which character?",
      answer1: "Vegeta",
      answer2: "Goku",
      answer3: "Gohan",
      answer4: "Androd 18",
      correctAnswer: "Androd 18"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "During the Namek Aftermath, who wasn’t wished back to life?",
      answer1: "Yamcha",
      answer2: "Krillin",
      answer3: "Goku",
      answer4: "Tien",
      correctAnswer: "Goku"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Can the Dragon Ball Radar detect Dragon Balls when they aren’t active?",
      answer1: "Yes",
      answer2: "No",
      answer3: "Sometimes",
      answer4: "Never",
      correctAnswer: "No"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Where is the Tournament of Power held?",
      answer1: "Sugoroku Space",
      answer2: "The Dead Zone",
      answer3: "The Null Realm",
      answer4: "Demon Realm",
      correctAnswer: "The Null Realm"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What did Kefla say to Goku right before he hits her with a Kamehameha?",
      answer1: "Now you die",
      answer2: "Get ready to die",
      answer3: "See you in hell",
      answer4: "You can't dodge in mid-air",
      correctAnswer: "You can't dodge in mid-air"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Universe 7 members worked together to eliminate Aniraza. Which character delivered the blow to the energy reactor on his forehead?",
      answer1: "Android 17",
      answer2: "Goku",
      answer3: "Frieze",
      answer4: "Vegeta",
      correctAnswer: "Android 17"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who invented the Kamehameha?",
      answer1: "Bardock",
      answer2: "Korin",
      answer3: "Goku",
      answer4: "Master Roshi",
      correctAnswer: "Master Roshi"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "According to Vegeta, why does Goku think less?",
      answer1: "He's an idiot",
      answer2: "Everything omes naturally to him",
      answer3: "He didn't say anything",
      answer4: "He's too busy thinking about dumb things",
      correctAnswer: "He's an idiot"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who possesses power that transcends time itself?",
      answer1: "Vegeta",
      answer2: "Hit",
      answer3: "Jiren",
      answer4: "Goku",
      correctAnswer: "Jiren"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "At his reveal, what did Goku Black say to Future Trunks?",
      answer1: "“Fighting you will be like taking candy from a child.”",
      answer2: "“Today is your last day on earth.”",
      answer3: "“Say goodbye to those you love.”",
      answer4: "“I’ll be the last thing you see before you die.”",
      correctAnswer: "“Today is your last day on earth.”"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Supreme Kais and their apprentices wear earrings called what?",
      answer1: "Senzu",
      answer2: "Nimbus",
      answer3: "Ensinji",
      answer4: "Potara",
      correctAnswer: "Potara"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "The signature move of Hit “Time-Skip” allows him to manipulate and skip time for how long?",
      answer1: "Two seconds",
      answer2: "Tenth of a second",
      answer3: "One Second",
      answer4: "Half of a second",
      correctAnswer: "Tenth of a second"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Before Beerus slapped Bulma, what was it that Buu wouldn’t share with Beerus?",
      answer1: "Pudding",
      answer2: "Cake",
      answer3: "Sushi",
      answer4: "BBQ",
      correctAnswer: "Pudding"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Who is a user of Zeno’s Button?",
      answer1: "Goku",
      answer2: "Beerus",
      answer3: "Vegeta",
      answer4: "Bulma",
      correctAnswer: "Goku"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Sacred Water is mystical water that is stored where?",
      answer1: "Amenbo Island",
      answer2: "The Lookout",
      answer3: "Koren Tower",
      answer4: "Protective Dome",
      correctAnswer: "The Lookout"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "The inhabitants of which planet created the liquid weapon known as Commeson?",
      answer1: "Planet Potaufeu",
      answer2: "Planet luud",
      answer3: "Planet Namchinno",
      answer4: "Planet Rygol 7",
      correctAnswer: "Planet Potaufeu"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Broly was raised on which planet?",
      answer1: "Konats",
      answer2: "Demon Realm",
      answer3: "Big Geta Star",
      answer4: "Vampa",
      correctAnswer: "Vampa"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is inside the Angel Attendant’s Staff?",
      answer1: "Pocket Dimension",
      answer2: "Nothing",
      answer3: "Time",
      answer4: "Pure Energy",
      correctAnswer: "Pocket Dimension"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What did Goku do to surpass Tien’s speed in the 23rd World Martial Arts Tournament?",
      answer1: "Using wolf Techniques",
      answer2: "oncentrating his chakras",
      answer3: "Using Cheetah Techniques",
      answer4: "Removed Weighted Clothing",
      correctAnswer: "Removed Weighted Clothing"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "The Energy Meter measures power levels in what measurement?",
      answer1: "Kili",
      answer2: "Battle Points",
      answer3: "Battle Power",
      answer4: "Riki",
      correctAnswer: "Kili"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "At the beginning of Dragon Ball Super, Hercule gives Goku 100 Million Zeni. Where did Hercule get the money from?",
      answer1: "World Peace Prize",
      answer2: "Gift from Zeno",
      answer3: "Gambling",
      answer4: "Fighting",
      correctAnswer: "World Peace Prize"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Gohan went to what high school in Satan City?",
      answer1: "Orange Star High School",
      answer2: "Mutaito Private Academy",
      answer3: "Turtle High School",
      answer4: "Panther-Fang High School",
      correctAnswer: "Orange Star High School"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is Trunk’s favorite food?",
      answer1: "Mochi",
      answer2: "Sushi",
      answer3: "Pizza",
      answer4: "Grilled Meat",
      correctAnswer: "Grilled Meat"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What are the six dots on Krillins forehead from?",
      answer1: "Birth Defect",
      answer2: "Scar from Training",
      answer3: "he did it for more power",
      answer4: "Incense Burn",
      correctAnswer: "Incense Burn"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Which character was brought into the series to replace Goku as the  character?",
      answer1: "Trunks",
      answer2: "Goten",
      answer3: "Krillin",
      answer4: "Roshi",
      correctAnswer: "Goten"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Goku is so kind because…",
      answer1: "He was dropped on his head as a baby",
      answer2: "Because of a healing event in the healing chumber",
      answer3: "There's no explanation",
      answer4: "He practiecs positive affrimations",
      correctAnswer: "He was dropped on his head as a baby"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is Vegetas fear?",
      answer1: "Worms",
      answer2: "Loud Music",
      answer3: "Birds",
      answer4: "Monkeys",
      correctAnswer: "Worms"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "With training, can a Saiyan control their Great Ape form?",
      answer1: "No",
      answer2: "Yes",
      answer3: "Sometimes",
      answer4: "Never",
      correctAnswer: "Yes"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Why was Chi-Chi renamed in the Latin American dub?",
      answer1: "It Wasn't Changed",
      answer2: "Chi-Chi was going to be removed",
      answer3: "Her name is hard to pronunce",
      answer4: "Chi-Chi means breast in Spanish",
      correctAnswer: "Chi-Chi means breast in Spanish"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Do all canon Saiyans have brown or black hair?",
      answer1: "Yes",
      answer2: "No",
      answer3: "Some of them",
      answer4: "Most of them",
      correctAnswer: "Yes"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "King Kais pet monkey Bubble is a reference to which celebrities pet monkey of the same name?",
      answer1: "Prince",
      answer2: "Michael Jackson",
      answer3: "Princess",
      answer4: "Goku",
      correctAnswer: "Michael Jackson"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "What is android 17s real name?",
      answer1: "Akeno",
      answer2: "Lapis",
      answer3: "Sinon",
      answer4: "Sora",
      correctAnswer: "Lapis"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "The Yu-Gi-Oh card Tyler the Great Warrior was modeled after which character?",
      answer1: "Caulifla",
      answer2: "Black Goku",
      answer3: "Vegeta",
      answer4: "Future trunks",
      correctAnswer: "Lapis"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Before the Saiyans took over, what was Planet Vegeta Called?",
      answer1: "Planet Thing",
      answer2: "Planet Vegeta",
      answer3: "Red Thing",
      answer4: "Planet Plant",
      correctAnswer: "Planet Plant"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "The character Bibidi, Babidi, and Buu got their names from which Disney movie?",
      answer1: "Snow White",
      answer2: "Pinnochio",
      answer3: "Sleeping Beauty",
      answer4: "Cinderella",
      correctAnswer: "Cinderella"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "How many different hairstyles has Bulma had?",
      answer1: "Seventeen",
      answer2: "Eight",
      answer3: "Four",
      answer4: "Thirty Two",
      correctAnswer: "Seventeen"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Goku is afraid of…",
      answer1: "Needles and Hospital Food",
      answer2: "Germs and Blood",
      answer3: "Lice and Heights",
      answer4: "Cars and Snails",
      correctAnswer: "Needles and Hospital Food"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "In the beginning, Dragon Ball was loosely based on which Chinese novel?",
      answer1: "The World of Suzie Wong",
      answer2: "Journey to the West",
      answer3: "Dream of the Red Chamber",
      answer4: "The Tail of Genji",
      correctAnswer: "Journey to the West"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Do Pure-blooded Saiyans hairstyles ever change?",
      answer1: "Yes",
      answer2: "No",
      answer3: "Some of them",
      answer4: "Most of them",
      correctAnswer: "No"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Goten was the youngest Super Saiyan. When did he have his first Super Saiyan transformation?",
      answer1: "Age of 4",
      answer2: "Age of 5",
      answer3: "Age of 7",
      answer4: "Age of 10",
      correctAnswer: "Age of 7"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Hercule had a different name. What was it?",
      answer1: "Sensei Ash",
      answer2: "Mr.Satan",
      answer3: "Master Mutaito",
      answer4: "Atsuko",
      correctAnswer: "Mr.Satan"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
      question: "Saiyans are born with naturally sensitive…",
      answer1: "Stomachs",
      answer2: "Egos",
      answer3: "Nipples",
      answer4: "Tails",
      correctAnswer: "Tails"
  ),
];

// 45 questions